

VAN TABBERT

MOBILE AND WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full stack web and mobile application developer with experience using modern JavaScript libraries and cloud integration. Analytical problem solver with the ability to quickly learn new technologies and languages. Skilled multitasker comfortable working within a team and independently. Enthusiastic mentor motivated to guide other developers to their full potential.

CONTACT ME

t: (817) 908-7911

e: van.tabbert@gmail.com

w: www.vannva.me

facebook.com/vannienicole

github.com/vannya

in linkedIn.com/in/vannya

twitter.com/vannyalock

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Strong: ReactJS, React Native, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, ES6, Redux, React Router V4, Reach Router, Node.js, Express, Sass, WordPress, Git/Version Control, Photoshop,

Knowledgable: C#, Electron, GraphQL, NoSQL, SQL, Webpack, Android, PHP, Java, C++. Sketch. Illustrator. Azure. Azure functions

CERTIFICATIONS

React Nanodegree Aug 2018 Front End Dev Nanodegree Jul 2018 Full Stack Dev Nanodegree May 2018 Android Basics Nanodegree Apr 2018 FCC Front End Certificate Feb 2018

VOLUNTEER

Mew Cat Rescue Feb 2019 - present Developer and Designer

Mercy House Aug 2014 - Oct 2017 Photographer

Girl Scouts of USA Aug 2010 - May 2012

Daisy and Brownie Leader

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

May 2018 - present

Walmart - Bentonville, AR

- Lead Frontend Developer of a nine person team building a custom ERP system integrating with microservice APIs (C#, Node, Python), legacy applications and third-party services.
- Lead Developer and Systems Architect for React UI Library suite encompassing designs for structural, presentational, chatbot and feedback components with dynamically rendered web documentation.
- Building modern backend APIs as Azure Functions (Node and C#) or standalone .NET Core Web APIs with extensive Swagger documentation to efficiently handle requests of up to 30,000 active users.
- Led 3 full-day workshops on design handoff between UX and development teams. Presented talks to multiple audiences promoting increased reusability in code and design.
- Support other teams' development projects as needed. I.e. project architecture mapping, specific feature development and application optimization.
- Mentor 5 junior developers and 1 junior designer with 1:1React teaching sessions and/or career and goal planning.

Mobile and Web Application Developer

Sept 2018 - present

Tabbert Technologies, LLC - Bentonville, AR

- Consulting for more than a dozen nonprofits and local businesses to create websites and applications using React, .NET Core (C#), and WordPress (JS/PHP).
- Focusing on reaching customers, donors, and recipients using modern UI/UX principles and SEO optimization for maximum reach.

Frontend Developer (Remote)

Jul 2017 - Jun 2018

Chingu - Toronto, Canada

- Front end development of the original Chingu Developer Network client using React and interfacing with a Node/GraphQL/PostgreSQL backend.
- Facilitate 8-10 week long Voyage cohorts of 350 persons across 75 nations.

PROJECTS

Chingu.io: Front end development of the Chingu Development Network client using React and interfacing with a Node/GraphQL/PostgreSQL backend.

Our Military Kids: Complete custom Word Press theme for national non-profit organization that has helped over 66,000 military children.

<u>Designsteins</u>: Design company custom WordPress theme built witth php and JavaScript.

IAmSoGal: Flexible WordPress custom theme for international venture capital firm.

ModMemes: Meme Library web application using MERN stack.

TuVotoTuldioma: WordPress based informational site for a non-profit, All Voting Is Local, using php, jQuery and HTML5/CSS3.

JuniperMail: Survey generation site using MERN stack with Stripe and Sendgrid.

Bearbnb: Clone of Airbnb using ReactJS/Redux, Express, Node.js and MongoDB.

Vannya.me: Portfolio site using React where additional work can be found.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science, Software Development Expected Sept 2020

Western Governors University

Associates of Applied Science, Software Development Dec 2017

North Lake College - Irving, TX

Associates of Arts, Liberal Studies May 2017

North Lake College - Irving, TX